A Guide to the Papers of Stanley Clay Walker
Special Collections and University Archives, J. Douglas and Patricia W. Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Legislative Papers 1960s to 1990s
  - Education 1964-1992
    - Recommendations and References-Colleges, Universities, and Schools (A-B) 1973-1976 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Recommendations and References-Colleges, Universities, and Schools (C-H) 1973-1976 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Recommendations and References-Colleges, Universities, and Schools (J-W) 1973-1976 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Recommendations and References-Colleges, Universities, and Schools 1988-1990, 1992 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Richard Bland College undated (Box-folder 24:11)
    - School Transportation-Busing 1967-1972 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - School Transportation-Busing 1973-1975 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Sex Education-Commission on 1970 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Southwest Virginia Community College undated (Box-folder 24:15)
    - State School Aid Fund, Basic Distribution of 1973 (Box-folder 24:16)
    - Special Education undated (Box-folder 25:1)
    - State Education Assistance 1974 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - State of Virginia: Education Information undated (Box-folder 23:3)
    - State Department of Education undated (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Student-Legislator Open Forum & Model Assembly 1972-1975 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Student Assistance for Projects 1974-1976 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Student Protest-An Institutional and National Profile, by Harold Hodgkinson-University of California, Berkley undated (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Teacher Immunity-HB 177 1972 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Tidewater Community College undated (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Tuition Assistance Data I 1973-1976 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Tuition Assistance Data II 1973-1976 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - University of Virginia undated (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Virginia Beach Public Schools undated (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University undated (Box-folder 25:14)
    - Virginia Community Colleges undated (Box-folder 25:15)
    - Virginia Council of Business Colleges undated (Box-folder 25:16)
    - Virginia Education Association undated (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science undated (Box-folder 25:18)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute undated (Box-folder 25:19)
    - Virginia State College undated (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Virginia Wesleyan College undated (Box-folder 25:21)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System 1972-1975 (Box-folder 25:22)
    - Vocational Technical Education Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 25:23)
    - Washington and Lee University undated (Box-folder 25:24)
    - William and Mary (College of) undated (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Employment 1970 to 1977
    Pertains to employment issues that the General Assembly of Virginia dealt with, such as benefits and compensation.
    - Employment Information undated (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Retirement and Employee Benefits 1970 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Virginia Employment Commission 1973-1977 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Wage and Hour 1975 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Workman’s Compensation undated (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Environment 1971 to 1976
    Pertains to environmental issues that the General Assembly of Virginia dealt with, including air and water pollution.
    - Air Pollution Control 1973 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Department of Conservation and Economic Development undated (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Gathright Project undated (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Lynnhaven River-Pollution 1976 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Offshore/Intercontinental Shelf 1974-1976 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Portsmouth Refinery 1976-1977 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Solid Waste Disposal 1972-1973 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - State Water Control Board undated (Box-folder 26:14)
    - Virginia Environmental Health Association Meeting April 23 1976 (Box-folder 26:15)
    - Water 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26:16)
    - Wetlands 1971-1974 (Box-folder 26:17)
  - General Assembly 1960s to 1990s
    Pertains to the issues that Walker dealt with, as both a member of the House and Senate. Issues include budgets, the Equal Rights Amendment, various bills and legislation, and constitutional revision.
    - Session 1973 (Box-folder 26:18)
    - Abortion 1973-1977 (Box-folder 26:19)
    - Age of Majority Legislation, 18 year olds 1972-1974 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Anti-Trust 1973 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Appointments 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Appointments-Governor 1966 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - Appointments-Governor Holton 1970-1971 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Appropriations Act 1974 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Appropriations Committee 1968-1970 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - Appropriations and Budget undated (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Arts-Funding undated (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Barrier-Free Design 1974 (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Bicentennial Data 1975 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Bill Drafted-Agency for Adult Physically Handicapped 1976 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Bill Drafted-re. Money Judgments in Spousal or Child Support 1976 (Box-folder 27:13)
    - Bill Drafted-re. VA Supplemental Retirement System 1976 (Box-folder 27:14)
    - Bills-General Assembly I undated (Box-folder 27:15)
    - Bills-General Assembly II undated (Box-folder 27:16)
    - Bills and Printouts, etc. 1974 (Box-folder 27:17)
    - Bills/Legislation 1990s (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Blue Law 1974-1975 (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Bond Issue-Campaign, etc I 1968 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Bond Issue-Campaign, etc. II 1968 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Bond Issue-Campaign, etc. III 1968 (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Folder 6: Bond Issue-Campaign, etc. IV 1968 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - Budget 1971-1972 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Budget Bill Amendments (HB 30) undated (Box-folder 28:8)
    - Folder 9: Budget-1972/1974 Biennium (HB 30) 1972 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Budget Requests 1975 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - Budget Tour 1973 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Capital Outlay Allocations 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Caucuses 1972 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - Caucuses, Committee Membership, & Related Matters-Prior Sessions 1976 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Child Care Centers-Important Data 1974-1976 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Christmas Cards- General Assembly 1990s (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Code of Virginia undated (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Folder 9: Constitutional Revision I 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Constitutional Revision II 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Constitutional Revision III 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Collective Bargaining 1974-1976 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - Commissioner of Revenue-Norfolk House Bills 1974 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - Congressional Re-districting, Extra Session 1965 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Constituent Assistance 1974-1975 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Consumer Legislation 1972 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Council of State Governments 1970-1971 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Court Reform and the New Setup 1973 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Digest of Acts of Assembly: 1964, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - Docket-Committee on General Laws 1976 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - Folder 8: Docket-Senate Committee on Education and Health (i.e. SB 269) 1976 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - Folder 9: Docket-Senate Committee on Rehabilitation and Social Services 1976 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - End of Session Courtesy Letter Exchange-Legislators and State Officers 1972 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - Equal Rights Amendment 1971-1973 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Equal Rights Amendment 1974-1976 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (For) 1973-1976 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Folder 3: Equal Rights Amendment (Against) 1973-1976 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Executive Budget Amendments and Bills 1990s (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Finance Committee: Budget Amendments I 1976 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Finance Committee: Budget Amendments II 1976 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Finances 1976 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Data Received 1970-1971 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - General Assembly Appointments undated (Box-folder 31:9)
    - General Assembly Calendars March 9, 1974 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - General Assembly Members undated (Box-folder 31:11)
    - General Assembly-Principal Actions 1974-1976 (Box-folder 31:12)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session I 1969 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session II 1969 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session III 1969 (Box-folder 32:3)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session IV 1969 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session V 1969 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session VI 1969 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - General Assembly-Extra Session VII 1969 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - General Assembly-Special Session I 1971 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - General Assembly-Special Session II 1971 (Box 33:3)
    - General Assembly-Special Session III 1971 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - General Assembly-Special Session IV 1971 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - General Assembly-Special Session V 1971 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - General Assembly-Special Session VI 1971 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - General Assembly-Special Session VII 1971 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - General Assembly Session 1974 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - General Laws 1976 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Governor Godwin 1973-1976 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Hairdressers Board, HB 71 & HB 73 1974 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Handicapped Bills undated (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Health-Welfare-Recreation Planning Council 1975-1977 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Hollywood Trip with Governor Wilder 1990 (Box-folder 34:7)
    - House of Delegates undated (Box-folder 34:8)
    - Hunger Conference 1975-1976 (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Inauguration of Governor Linwood Holton, Jr. 1970 (Box-folder 34:10)
    - Inauguration of Governor Mills E. Godwin, Jr. 1974 (Box-folder 34:11)
    - Issues undated (Box-folder 34:12)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day March 15, 1975 (Box-folder 34:13)
    - Job Applicants 1975-1976 (Box-folder 34:14)
    - Judge-Appointment 1966 (Box-folder 34:15)
    - Judgeship Nominations and Related Data 1974-1976 (Box-folder 34:16)
    - King’s Dominion 1976 (Box-folder 34:17)
    - Landlord and Tenant Act 1974 (Box-folder 34:18)
    - Various Legislation 1976 (Box-folder 34:19)
    - Legislative Programs 1972 (Box-folder 34:20)
    - Legislative Public Hearings 1971 (Box-folder 34:21)
    - Legislative Services, Division of 1971-1977 (Box-folder 34:22)
    - Legislation Status Reports 1973 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Folder 2: Legislative Summaries (Various) I 1974 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Legislative Summaries (Various) II 1974 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Library of Virginia undated (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Licensing of Accountants SB 26 Carryover to 1975 Session 1974 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Lifetime Hunting & Fishing License Bill 1972-1974 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Lobbyists 1975-1976 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Various Legislation 1971-1973 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Marine Issues and Educational Programs 1975 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Motion Picture Rating Study Subcommittee-HB 1081 1972-1973 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Motor Vehicle Repair Industry Practices-SB 35, Carryover to 1975 Session 1974 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - National Guard 1974 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - No Fault Insurance 1974 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences/Chrysler Museum undated (Box-folder 35:14)
    - Norfolk Savings and Loan Debacle 1973-1974 (Box-folder 35:15)
    - Notary Public Recommendations 1972-1977 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - Ombudsman 1972 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Pages 1973 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Political Campaign Financing 1974 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Polygraph Licensing Law-HB 304 1974 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Professional and Occupational Registration Surveyors Bill 1972 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Professional Negotiations (SB 180) I 1972 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Professional Negotiations (SB 180) II 1972 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Professional Negotiations (SB 180) III 1972 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Proposed Bills to be Introduced 1965-1966 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Real Estate License (HB 940) 1974 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Recommendations and References-General March 18, 1970-March 16, 1973 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Recommendations and References-General March 22, 1973-January 23, 1976 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Recommendations and References to Governor Holton 1972 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - Requests-New 1969-1975 (Box-folder 36:14)
    - Roll Calls-General Assembly undated (Box-folder 36:15)
    - Rules Committee and Caucus 1975-1976 (Box-folder 36:16)
    - Salary Issues 1974 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Schedules undated (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Seating Arrangement of the Senate-General Assembly of 1972 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Session Summaries 1970 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Southeastern Public Service Authority of Virginia 1976 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Standing/Steering Committees undated (Box-folder 37:6)
    - State Aid for Libraries undated (Box-folder 37:7)
    - State Milk Commission-Price Increase 1973 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - State Senate undated (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Topics to be discussed undated (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Veterans Benefits Bills undated (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council undated (Box 37:12)
    - Virginia Beach undated (Box-folder 37:13)
    - Virginia Beach Judgeships and Judiciary Re-elections and Appointments 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37:14)
    - Virginia Cabinet undated (Box-folder 37:15)
    - Virginia Code Commission 1973 (Box-folder 37:16)
    - Virginia Lotto undated (Box-folder 37:17)
    - Weekly Patron Report February 21, 1976 (Box-folder 37:18)
    - Welfare undated (Box-folder 37:19)
    - Department of Welfare and Institutions-Correspondence/Recommendations 1973 (Box-folder 37:20)
    - G. William Whitehurst 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37:21)
  - Health 1969-1976
    Pertains to the issues involving General Assembly legislation, as well as the founding of Eastern Virginia Medical School.
    - Behavioral Sciences Professions Bill, HB 378 1976 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Bureau of Vital Records and Health Statistics 1974 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Central Virginia Health Systems Agency, Inc. 1976 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Community Mental Health Center undated (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Death with Dignity, Bill-HB 620 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Department of Health 1971-1976 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School I undated (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School II undated (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School III undated (Box-folder 38:9)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School IV undated (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School V undated (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School VI undated (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Family Practice Program 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Health Benefits undated (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Health Education Study, HJR 244 1975 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Health/Medical/Hospital Legislation 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Legislative Program-Virginia Hospital Association 1972 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Medical College of Virginia 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Medical Malpractice Insurance I 1975 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Medical Malpractice Insurance II 1975 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Medical Malpractice Insurance III 1975 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Mental Health undated (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Norfolk Area Medical Center Authority 1969-1970 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Norfolk Area Medical Center Authority 1970 - 1971 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Nursing Homes Data 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Sudden Infant Death Syndrome 1974 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care 1975 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Labor 1972-1977
    Pertains to the issues in regard to labor in Virginia.
    - A.F.L.-C.I.O. 1972-1976 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Community Services Counselors Course (United Communities Fund; A.F.L.-C.I.O.) 1977 (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Unions and Labor 1972 (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Parks and Recreation 1975
    Pertains to the issues in regard to parks and recreation facilities in Virginia.
    - Recreation Information undated (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Therapeutic Recreation Institute National Recreation and Park Association Southern District Recreation and Park Association March 23-25, 1975 (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Services 1971-1975
    Pertains to the issues in regard to services provided to the state of Virginia, such as electricity, utilities, and sanitation.
    - Hampton Roads Sanitation District 1971-1972 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - VEPCO Issues 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40:12)
  - State Related 1967
    Pertains to state-related issues within Virginia.
    - County of Henrico/City of Richmond-Merger and Annexation 1967 (Box-folder 40:13)
  - Tax/Revenue 1972-1976
    Pertains to tax/revenue issues and legislation.
    - Coal Severance Tax Bill 1976 (Box-folder 40:14)
    - Deeds and Recordation 1975 (Box-folder 40:15)
    - General Fund Revenues undated (Box-folder 40:16)
    - Sales Tax undated (Box-folder 40:17)
    - Study on Local License Fees and Taxes for Contractors (SJR 142) 1973 (Box-folder 40:18)
    - Taxes 1972 (Box-folder 40:19)
    - Tax/Revenue: City of Norfolk undated (Box-folder 40:20)
  - Transportation 1968-76, 1995
    Pertains to transportation issues and legislation in Virginia, such as highways and mass transit.
    - Airports 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41:1)
    - Alcohol and Highway Safety 1972 (Box-folder 41:2)
    - Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel Project 1969 (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation I undated (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation II undated (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Department of Highways and Transportation-Norfolk/Virginia Beach Expressway Study Commission 1976 (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Hampton Roads-Tunnels 1972-1977 (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Highway Safety undated (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Maritime Terminals, Inc.-Security Force 1973 (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Mass Transit undated (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Norfolk Port and Industrial Authority 1971-1976 (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Public Hearings 1968 (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Tidewater Transit District Commission and Transportation Material 1973-1976 (Box-folder 41:13)
    - Virginia Port Authority 1973-1976 (Box-folder 41:14)
    - Washington Airports Task Force-1995 Air Service Development Report 1995 (Box-folder 41:15)
- Legislative Files 1964-1971, 1993-2000
  Consists of loose books and binders of compiled materials that Walker kept in regard to issues within the General Assembly and his Senate campaigns. The items are stored in artifact cases and archival binder cases.
  Chronological
  - Virginia Senate-Senate Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964 (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Virginia Senate-Senate Bills and Joint Resolutions 1964 (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Extra Session-1969: House Bills, Resolutions, and Documents 1969 (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Extra Session-1969: Senate Bills, Resolutions, and Documents 1969 (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Home and Address Cards for Precinct 23- Redistricting Special 1971 (Box-folder 44:3)
  - General Assembly of Virginia, Manual of Senate and House of Spring 1970 (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Report of the Secretary of the Commonwealth 1993-94 (Box-folder 45:1)
  - Report of the Secretary of the Commonwealth 1994-95 (Box-folder 45:2)
  - A Legislator’s Guide to Public Education in Virginia December, 1993 (Box-folder 46:1)
  - Budget Requests 1996-2000 (Box-folder 47:1)
  - Thank You File 1998 (Box-folder 48:1)
  - Cooper and Secrest Associates Inc.: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Virginia’s 6th Senate District” June, 1999 (Box-folder 49:1)
  - Fiscal Issues Facing the Commonwealth November 18-19, 1999 (Box-folder 50:1)
  - Shipbuilding Commission 1999 (Box-folder 51:1)
  - Walker for Senate Consultation Folder 1995, 1999 (Box-folder 52:1)
  - (Unlabeled) Virginia Democratic Caucus Consultation Folder 1999 (Box-folder 53:1)
- Virginia State Crime Commission 1966 to 1992
  Consists of papers relating to issues that Walker dealt with as a member of the Virginia State Crime Commission, which dealt with issues such as capital punishment, juvenile crime, pari-mutuel betting, and sex crimes.
  Chronological - alpha
  - General 1968 to 1977
    Pertains to information regarding to the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Applications 1973-1976 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - Citizen Requests 1968, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - Commission Appointments 1974 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - Minutes September 5, 1968-June 9, 1969 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Minutes 1972-1977 (Box-folder 54:5)
    - Programs/Studies…Proposed/Considered 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54:6)
    - Proposals Received 1967-1968 (Box-folder 54:7)
    - Recommendations 1969 (Box-folder 54:8)
  - Arson undated
    Pertains to information regarding the issue of arson in Virginia.
    - Arson undated (Box-folder 54:9)
  - Capital Punishment 1973 to 1974
    Pertains to information regarding the issue of capital punishment in Virginia.
    - Capital Punishment 1973-1974 (Box-folder 54:10)
  - Child/Domestic Abuse 1973 to 1975
    Pertains to information regarding the issue of child/domestic Abuse in Virginia.
    - Child Abuse 1973-1975 (Box-folder 54:11)
  - Committees 1971 to 1977
    Pertains to the committees within or worked with the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Americans for Effective Law Enforcement, Inc. (Virginia Chapter) 1975 (Box-folder 54:12)
    - Council of State Governments 1974 (Box-folder 54:13)
    - Council on Criminal Justice I undated (Box-folder 55:1)
    - Council on Criminal Justice II undated (Box-folder 55:2)
    - Council on Criminal Justice III undated (Box-folder 55:3)
    - Council on Criminal Justice IV undated (Box-folder 55:4)
    - Council on Criminal Justice V undated (Box-folder 55:5)
    - Council on Criminal Justice VI undated (Box-folder 55:6)
    - Report of the Grand Jury Study Committee 1975 (Box-folder 55:7)
    - John Howard Association I undated (Box-folder 56:1)
    - John Howard Association II undated (Box-folder 56:2)
    - National Society of State Legislators undated (Box-folder 56:3)
    - Organized Crime Detection Task Force I undated (Box-folder 56:4)
    - Organized Crime Detection Task Force II undated (Box-folder 56:5)
    - Organized Crime Detection Task Force III undated (Box-folder 56:6)
    - Report of the Organized Crime Detection Task Force 1971 (Box-folder 56:7)
    - Probation and Parole Board 1972-1973 (Box-folder 56:8)
    - Special Study Unit Recommendations undated (Box-folder 56:9)
    - Report of the Subcommittee to Study Sentencing 1977 (Box-folder 56:10)
    - Virginia Task Force on Criminal Justice Goals and Objectives 1976 (Box-folder 56:11)
  - Conferences 1971 to 1975
    Pertains to the conferences that Walker attended for the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Advanced Organized Crime Seminar July 22-25, 1973 (Box-folder 56:12)
    - National Organized Crime Prevention Council October 13-16, 1974 (Box-folder 56:13)
    - Organized Crime Detection Task Force October 8-9, 1974 (Box-folder 57:1)
    - Virginia Conference on Corrections April 26-29, 1973 (Box-folder 57:2)
    - Folder 3: Status Offender Project Seminar, June 27-29, 1976-Legis 50: Center for Legislative Improvement June 27-29, 1976 (Box-folder 57:3)
    - Virginia Association of Drug Abuse Enforcement Officers 1971-1975 (Box-folder 57:4)
  - Crime Labs undated
    Pertains to the issue of crime labs in Virginia.
    - Crime Laboratories undated (Box-folder 57:5)
  - Data 1967 to 1991
    Contains reports and statistics for the Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - Annual Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1978 (Box-folder 57:6)
    - Annual Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1982 and 1983 (Box-folder 57:7)
    - Annual Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1988 and 1989 (Box-folder 57:8)
    - Annual Report of the Virginia State Crime Commission 1991 (Box-folder 57:9)
    - Central Criminal Records Exchange 1970-1972 (Box-folder 57:10)
    - Comprehensive Long Range Master Plan for the Adult Criminal Justice System in Virginia 1974 (Box-folder 57:11)